Guide to the Associate University Librarian for Collection Development, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Record of Michael Keller as associate university librarian, circa 1985-1993; Accession 1994-A-074
  - Transfer Materials 89-90 (Box 5, Folder 187)
  - Turner Subscriptions (Box 5, Folder 188)
  - Yale Academic Plan 1989 (Box 5, Folder 189)
  - Yale Center for International and Area Studies (Box 5, Folder 190)
  - Yale College Course of Instruction 1828 (Box 5, Folder 191)
  - Yale Libraries - Official List (Box 5, Folder 192)
  - Yale Revisited (Box 5, Folder 193)
  - Yale University - Financial Operations (Box 5, Folder 194)
  - Yale University Press (Box 5, Folder 195)
  - Yale University - Proposed Majors (Box 5, Folder 196)
  - YUL -Bibliographic Utilities Group (Box 5, Folder 197)
  - YUL - Foreign Vendor Data (86/87 85/86 84/85) (Box 5, Folder 198)
  - YUL - Invoices Approved on 2-7-92 summed by fund (Box 5, Folder 199)
  - YUL - January 1992 Summary Rainbow Report (Box 5, Folder 200)
  - YUL - Mid-year Summary Income and Expense Report, January 1992 (Box 5, Folder 201)
  - YUL - Special Charges for Out of Building Use (Box 5, Folder 202)
- Records of the Associate University Librarian for Collection Development, Yale University, 1987-1993; Accession 1995-A-066
  - -Acquisitions FY 90-91 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - -Acquisitions FY 91-92 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Acquisitions Support Group 1989-90 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - -African Collection FY 91-92 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - -African Collection FY 92-93 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - -ALA Mid-Winter Meeting Jan 1990 & Jan 1991 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - -ALA Mid-Winter Meeting Jan 1993 - Denver Colorado (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - -Arabic Islamic Studies FY 87-88 to FY 88-89 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - -Arabic Islamic Studies FY 89-90 to FY 90-91 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - -Art & Architecture Library FY 87-88 to FY 92-93 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - -Divinity Library FY 92-93 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - -Divinity Library Annual Report FY 92-93 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - -East Asian Collection FY 91-92 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - -Judaica Collection Fy 89-90 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - -Judaica Collection FY 90-91, FY 91-92 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - -Judaica Collection FY 92-93 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - -Kline Science Library FY 89-90 to FY 91-92 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - -Manuscripts & Archives FY 90-91 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - -Manuscripts & Archives FY 91-92 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - -Music Library FY 91-92 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - -Preservation Department up to FY 90-91 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - -Slavic Collection FY 87-88, FY 88-89 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - -Slavic Collection FY 89-90 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - -Slavic Collection FY 90-91 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - -Slavic Collection FY 91-92 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - -Social Science Library FY 88-89 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - -Social Science Library FY 89-90 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - -Social Science Library FY 90-91 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - -Social Science Library FY 91-92 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - -SouthEast Asia Collection FY 90-91 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - -ARL Foreign Acquisitions '92 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - -ARL Foreign Acquisitions FY 92-93 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - -B.H. Blackwell FY 88-89 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - -B.H. Blackwell FY 89-90 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - -B.H. Blackwell FY 90-91 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - -B.H. Blackwell FY 91-92 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - -Library Book Budget FY 88-89 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - -Library Book Budget FY 89-90 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - -Library Budget FY 90-91 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Records of the associate university librarian for collection development, circa 1978-1997; Accession 1999-A-086 (Box 1–12)
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2032
- Records of Michael Keller as associate university librarian for collection development, circa 1971-1996; Accession 2004-A-074
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2031
  - Arundel Press (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Berkeley Finding Aid Project Conference (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - BNA: Approval Plans, 1991/2 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - BHB Statements, 1993/4 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - BNA -Blackwell North America (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - BNA - Profiles (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - BHB - Periodicals (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Casalini Annual Statistics (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - CRL -Middle East Microform Project (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - CRL -Purchase Proposals, 1991/2 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - CRL -Foreign Newspapers currently received on microfilm (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - CRL -Purchase Proposals, 1990/1 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - CRL Membership (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - CRL -Purchase Proposals, 1989/90 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - CRL -Purchase Proposals, 1987/8 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - CRL Online catalogue content form (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - English poetry database (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Collaborative projects - Emory (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Elsevier, 1991/2 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Elsevier, 1990/1 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Environmental Health and safety (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Faxon Co. (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Federal wage and hour audit (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Federation of Indian Publ. (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Export -Import Bank/ India (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Prabhu book service (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Patrologia Latina database (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Flood: Immediate Action Manual (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - H: Approval plan, 1989/90 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - H: Approval plan, 1990/1 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Harrassowitz: Approval Plan, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Approval plan: Romance languages and literatures (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Approval plans: School and Dept. libraries (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Slavic Approval Plan (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Approval plans: RFP/ Technical factors (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Approval Plan: UK books (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Human relations area files (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Livraria Portugal (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Monograph and Serial costs, 1986-93 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Governet blue ribbon commission (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Benelux 1990 titles to Nedbook (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - NIDS Booklet (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Norlis Agreement (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Archives Inventory (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Recon, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Papers (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - YUL - Statistics (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - RLG: German studies LTSP (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - RLG-CMDC: Washington, November 1990 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - RLG-CMDC: Palo Alto, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - RLG-CMDC: Baltimore, Fall 1989 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - RLG-CMDC: 1% for RLG (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - RLG-CMDC Social Science bibliographers (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - RLG: verification study in Agricultural Economics and Rural Sociology (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - RLG verification study in Romanesque sculpture (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - CMDC miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - RLG Conspectus (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - RLG-CMDC Conspectus sub-committee (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - RLG Engineering (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - RLG German Conspectus (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - RLG: Eureka (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - RLG: Long-term serials project business (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - RLG: Chemistry LISP (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - RLG Member data survey (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - RLG membership, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Sotheby's Saur, K. G. Ltd (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Vendor relations (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - YCIAS (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - YUL: Space (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Yale Center for International and Area Studies (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - YUL: Committees and Task forces (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Urban Advisory Committee (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - YUL Holdings (value) (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Title VI Programs (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Law Library (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Walpole Library (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Manuscripts and Archives, 1993/4 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Manuscripts and Archives, 1992/3 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Manuscripts and Archives -Heinz papers (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Fortunoff video archive for Holocaust testimonies (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Manuscripts and Archives: List of Manuscript collections (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Manager, Systems and Records Management -Manuscripts and Archives (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Manuscripts and Archives -Microform Collection Policy (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Map Collection (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Maps, machine readable (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Math Library (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Bio-Bibliography of Vesalius (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Medical Library (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Medical Library: History of Medicine and Science PhD. (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Medical Library: Publication Projects (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Medieval Studies (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Mellon Music Endowment (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Music Library, 1994/5 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Music Library, 1993/4 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Music Library, 1992/3 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Music Librarian search, Spring 1994 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - NEH Application: Music Library (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Numismatics (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Numismatic Acknowledgement (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Numismatic in/ out (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Numismatics/ New access codes (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Office of the President (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Early retirement plan, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Preservation, 1994/5 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Preservation Department, 1993/4 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - South Asian Studies Committee (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - SEA, 1992/3 (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - Southeast Asian Collection, 1993/4 (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - SEA, 1991/92 (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - Alteration requests (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - Systems office projects (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - Technical Services (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - A - L (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - Texas A & M University (Box 2, Folder 115)
  - Provost -Lloyd Suttle (Box 2, Folder 116)
  - Reference Department (Box 2, Folder 117)
  - Zeiglographia (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - Slavic and East European Collection, 1993/4 (Box 2, Folder 119)
  - Slavic Collection, 1992/3 (Box 2, Folder 120)
  - Slides and Photographs (Box 2, Folder 123)
  - Social Science Library, 1993/4 (Box 2, Folder 124)
  - Social Science Library, 1992/3 (Box 2, Folder 125)
  - IRS forms 8283 (Box 2, Folder 126)
  - Einstein Papers (Box 3, Folder 163)
  - Government Documents (Box 3, Folder 170)
  - Lacy slide collection (Box 3, Folder 199)
  - Lakeside classics (Box 3, Folder 200)
  - Newman bookplate (Box 3, Folder 226)
  - AVL Search/ Job description (Box 4, Folder 227)
  - African Collection (Box 4, Folder 228)
  - African Collection, 1993/4 (Box 4, Folder 229)
  - AMC Search, 1992/3 (Box 4, Folder 230)
  - Arabic/ Islamic, 1993/4 (Box 4, Folder 231)
  - Arabic/ Islamic studies, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 232)
  - Dar Mahjar -Arabic dealer (Box 4, Folder 233)
  - Makdisi collection (Box 4, Folder 234)
  - Persian collection (Box 4, Folder 235)
  - Sulaiman's Bookshop (Box 4, Folder 236)
  - A & A Librarian interview, 1993/4 (Box 4, Folder 237)
  - Artistic Archives of Fritz Eichenberg in the arts of the book (Box 4, Folder 239)
  - Johan Deumens -Artists' Books (Box 4, Folder 240)
  - Arts of the book, 1992/3 (Box 4, Folder 241)
  - Art of the book collection, 1988-92 (Box 4, Folder 242)
  - Bookplate collection (Box 4, Folder 243)
  - Babylonian collection (Box 4, Folder 244)
  - Public svs librarian interview, February 1993 (Box 4, Folder 245)
  - Beinecke Library (Box 4, Folder 246)
  - Circulation department (Box 4, Folder 248)
  - Classsics Library, 1993/4 (Box 4, Folder 249)
  - Classics Library, 1992/3 (Box 4, Folder 250)
  - CD ROM -Collection Development Server (Box 4, Folder 251)
  - Collection Impact (Box 4, Folder 252)
  - Systems -Collection Development (Box 4, Folder 253)
  - Collection Development - General (Box 4, Folder 254)
  - Collection Development Policy rewrite (Box 4, Folder 255)
  - Cross Campus Library (Box 4, Folder 256)
  - Divinity Lib/ Luce Proposal (Box 4, Folder 257)
  - Divinity Library, 1993/4 (Box 4, Folder 258)
  - Drama library (Box 4, Folder 259)
  - EAC Annual Report, 1993/4 (Box 4, Folder 260)
  - East Asian Collection, 1993/4 (Box 4, Folder 261)
  - East Asian Collection, 1992/3 (Box 4, Folder 262)
  - East Asian (Box 4, Folder 263)
  - Engineering and Applied Science Library (Box 4, Folder 266)
  - Environmental Studies Resources in Yale Libraries (Box 4, Folder 267)
  - EPH Library (Box 4, Folder 268)
  - Geology Library (Box 4, Folder 269)
  - Germanic Languages and Literatures (Box 4, Folder 270)
  - Gifts: Inter library (Box 4, Folder 271)
  - Government Documents: Mudd Library (Box 4, Folder 272)
  - Government Documents Center, 1989-93 (Box 4, Folder 273)
  - Historical Sound Recordings, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 274)
  - Historical Sound Recordings, 1993/4 (Box 4, Folder 275)
  - Historical Sound Recordings, 1992/3 (Box 4, Folder 276)
  - Historical Sound Recordings - Background (Box 4, Folder 277)
  - Judaica Collection, 1993/4 (Box 4, Folder 278)
  - Judaica Curator search, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 279)
  - Judaica: Mazer Curatorship (Box 4, Folder 282)
  - Kline Science Library, 1992-94 (Box 4, Folder 283)
  - Latin American, 1992/3 (Box 4, Folder 285)
  - Latin American Collection, 1993/4 (Box 4, Folder 286)
  - Green paper (Box 5, Folder 287)
  - Council on East Asian Affairs (Box 5, Folder 288)
  - Course of study committee (Box 5, Folder 289)
  - Development, 1994-96 (Box 5, Folder 290)
  - Digital Library manifesto (Box 5, Folder 291)
  - Digital Resources group (Box 5, Folder 292)
  - Electronic classroom (Box 5, Folder 293)
  - Electronic collections (Box 5, Folder 294)
  - Electronic policy (Box 5, Folder 295)
  - Electronic publishing (Box 5, Folder 296)
  - Electronic info @ Yale (Box 5, Folder 297)
  - Elsevier, 1993/4 (Box 5, Folder 298)
  - Elsevier, Pre-1990 (Box 5, Folder 299)
  - Erasmus -Dutch dealer (Box 5, Folder 300)
  - Miscellaneous Gift fund (Box 5, Folder 311)
  - SRLBEI (Box 5, Folder 318)
  - Gerits, 1990/1 (Box 5, Folder 322)
  - Gerits, 1989/90 (Box 5, Folder 323)
  - Gift opportunity list, 10/11/94 (Box 5, Folder 324)
  - Gift receipts, 1992/3 (Box 5, Folder 325)
  - Gifts, 1991/2 (Box 5, Folder 326)
  - Gifts Miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 327)
  - Lexis-Nexis (Box 5, Folder 328)
  - Library Management Council (Box 5, Folder 329)
  - LPBC, 1994/5 (Box 5, Folder 330)
  - Library of Congress (Box 5, Folder 331)
  - Library Collections Statisitcs (Box 5, Folder 332)
  - Library reorganisation, 1995/6 (Box 5, Folder 333)
  - Manuscripts and Archival Holdings, 1989/90 (Box 5, Folder 334)
  - Microfilm procedures (Box 5, Folder 335)
  - Modern language association (Box 5, Folder 336)
  - Munksgaard Agreement (Box 5, Folder 337)
  - Munksgaard Correspondence (Box 5, Folder 338)
  - Nedbook Correspondence, 1993/4 (Box 5, Folder 339)
  - Networked Electronic resources (Box 5, Folder 340)
  - Nedbook Approval plans (Box 5, Folder 341)
  - NIJHOFF (Box 5, Folder 342)
  - NIJHOFF Serials transformed (Box 5, Folder 343)
  - NIJHOFF Contins (Box 5, Folder 344)
  - Acknowledgements (Box 6, Folder 346)
  - Academic press ideal contact materials (Box 6, Folder 347)
  - Approval plans: Pre-pays, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 348)
  - Almqvist & Wiksell International (Box 6, Folder 349)
  - Alumni in London (Box 6, Folder 350)
  - Approval plans: American and British books (Box 6, Folder 351)
  - Approval plans: Dutch (Box 6, Folder 352)
  - Approval plans: Arabic language (Box 6, Folder 353)
  - Approval plan: Social sciences and philosophy (Box 6, Folder 354)
  - Approval plans: general (Box 6, Folder 355)
  - Approval plans: New Zealand (Box 6, Folder 356)
  - Approval plan: Tracking (Box 6, Folder 357)
  - ARL (Box 6, Folder 358)
  - ARL, 1996/7 (Box 6, Folder 359)
  - ARL -Serials Prices (Box 6, Folder 360)
  - Blackwells Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 361)
  - Blackwell Approval Profiles (Box 6, Folder 362)
  - Blackwell Approval Profiles (Box 6, Folder 363)
  - BNA/ NTO (Box 6, Folder 364)
  - Blackwell (Box 6, Folder 365)
  - Blackwell Approval Plan, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 366)
  - Book sales miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 367)
  - Casalini pre-payments, 1989/90 (Box 6, Folder 368)
  - Casalini Libri Deposit accounts, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 369)
  - Orbis, 1994/5 (Box 7, Folder 370)
  - Orbis Acquisition (Box 7, Folder 371)
  - Orbis coordinating group (Box 7, Folder 372)
  - Orbis -Audit, 1989/90 (Box 7, Folder 373)
  - Orbis - Database, 1988/90 (Box 7, Folder 374)
  - Orbis Exception reports, 1989/90 (Box 7, Folder 375)
  - Orbis -General, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 377)
  - Orbis -Merged headings (Box 7, Folder 378)
  - Orbis planning, 1989/90 (Box 7, Folder 379)
  - Orbis -RLNI LI, 1989/90 (Box 7, Folder 380)
  - Orbis Expense Transfer (Box 7, Folder 381)
  - Orbis, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 382)
  - Orbis -Matps conversion (Box 7, Folder 383)
  - Project X (Box 7, Folder 384)
  - Recon (Box 7, Folder 385)
  - RLA (Retro link associates) (Box 7, Folder 386)
  - Recon, 1992/3 (Box 7, Folder 387)
  - Recon, 1993/4 (Box 7, Folder 388)
  - RLG Biotech Prog (Box 7, Folder 389)
  - RLG CMDC -Round robin (Box 7, Folder 390)
  - RLG CMDC - Maths (Box 7, Folder 391)
  - RLG CMDC -English and American bibliographer (Box 7, Folder 392)
  - RLG CADS -Collection Access and Delivery svs (Box 7, Folder 393)
  - RLG CMDC -Minutes of meeting, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 394)
  - RLG CMDC -Mission and Objective (Box 7, Folder 395)
  - RLG -International Relations (Box 7, Folder 396)
  - RLG -Music Program Committee (Box 7, Folder 397)
  - RLG / PAE -Programs Advisory group (Box 7, Folder 398)
  - RLG - Prima (Box 7, Folder 399)
  - RLG -RLIN Rates (Box 7, Folder 400)
  - RLG -Operations update (Box 7, Folder 401)
  - RLG Task force (Box 7, Folder 402)
  - RLG TF (Box 7, Folder 403)
  - RLG TF on collection interdependence (Box 7, Folder 404)
  - RLG/ YUL symposium (Box 7, Folder 405)
  - RLG -long term serials project manual -final version (Box 7, Folder 406)
  - RLG -long term serials project business- chemistry- math diskettes (Box 7, Folder 407)
  - RLG serials (Box 7, Folder 408)
  - RLG MDPG -recommended reading (Box 7, Folder 409)
  - RLG MDPG - members (Box 7, Folder 410)
  - RLG Mid-decade Planning group, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 411)
  - Select l archive (Box 7, Folder 412)
  - Yale fact file (Box 7, Folder 413)
  - YUL academic plan (Box 7, Folder 414)
  - SML renovations (Box 7, Folder 415)
  - Capital campaign -YUL, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 416)
  - YUL - Affiliations (Box 7, Folder 417)
  - YUL -Working group on library delivery (Box 7, Folder 418)
  - YUL -Annual reports (Box 7, Folder 419)
  - Academic press titles (Box 7, Folder 420)
  - Space planning (Box 7, Folder 421)
  - Touzot, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 422)
  - Vendors miscellaneous, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 423)
  - UMI: General (Box 7, Folder 425)
  - SPD: Approval plans, 1993/4 (Box 7, Folder 426)
  - Yale Corporation (Box 7, Folder 427)
  - YUL articles (Box 7, Folder 428)
  - H: Correspondence, 1991/2 (Box 8, Folder 429)
  - OH -Electronic Data interchange for library and booksellers in Europe, 8 (Box 8, Folder 430)
  - Harrasowitz, 1992/3 (Box 8, Folder 431)
  - H: "DP" Statements, 1992/3 (Box 8, Folder 432)
  - Approval plan correspondence, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 433)
  - BAB Approval plan, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 434)
  - Harrasowitz AP, 1993/4 (Box 8, Folder 435)
  - Harvard University task group (Box 8, Folder 436)
  - Harvard University/ Cambridge information (Box 8, Folder 437)
  - Documenting Israel -Harvard College Library, 10-12 May 1993 (Box 8, Folder 438)
  - unspecified (Box 8, Folder 439)
  - Strategic plan for Harvard library, February 1992 (Box 8, Folder 440)
  - Harvard-Yale-MIT (Box 8, Folder 441)
  - HCAC, 1990/1 (Box 8, Folder 442)
  - Iberbook: Prepayment, 1992/3 (Box 8, Folder 443)
  - Iberbook: Miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 444)
  - Iberbook Correspondence, 1992/3 (Box 8, Folder 445)
  - Iberbook A.P., 1993/94 (Box 8, Folder 446)
  - Iberbook history A.P., 1991 (Box 8, Folder 447)
  - Iberbook Approval plan, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 448)
  - Iberbook Approval plan, 1990/1 (Box 8, Folder 449)
  - Iberbook Approval Plan, 1989/90 (Box 8, Folder 450)
  - Insurance (Box 8, Folder 451)
  - Internal Library transfers (Box 8, Folder 452)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on International planning (Box 8, Folder 453)
  - Jeffrey Norman & Co., Inc (Bibliography of Vesalius) (Box 8, Folder 456)
  - Norman publishing (bibliography of Vesalius) (Box 8, Folder 457)
  - Journal pricing (Box 8, Folder 458)
  - Kennys bookshop (Box 8, Folder 459)
  - Kennys, 1992/3 (Box 8, Folder 460)
  - Kennys, 1991/2 (Box 8, Folder 461)
  - Kennys, 1990/1 (Box 8, Folder 462)
  - Lexis/ Nexis (Box 8, Folder 463)
  - Sachs (Box 8, Folder 464)
  - Schmidt, Benno C. (Jr.) (Box 8, Folder 465)
  - Schoolfield, George (Box 8, Folder 468)
  - Sussheim Turkish Ottoman Empire (Box 8, Folder 482)
  - Swafford (Box 8, Folder 483)
- Records of Ann S. Okerson as associate university librarian for collection development, circa 1990-1995, Accession 2004-A-099
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2030
  - ALO, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Budget, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Book Budget Allocation, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Budget 96/97, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1996/97 Budget (Newsletter 1/93) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - CDC/ Minutes, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - CDC/ OSC, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Collection Descriptions, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Copy, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Documents, 1994-1997 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Employee Activity Sheets, 1992-1995 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - File Indexes, circa 1998 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - LibTech, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Notes (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Personnel, 1993 August (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Recent Faxes, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - ROM DG 6/93, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Special Collections, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Systems, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Usage Statistics, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Yale University Library Hours, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Equipment manuals for various machines, 1980-1984 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - RLG - MSS and Archives, 1990 January (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Lodging, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Commitments and Expenditures, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Conferences, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Pierson College, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Academic Press, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Personal, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Sound Recovery Permission Grants, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Maps (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Action Plans 1994/95 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Action Plans 1995 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Acquisitions, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - African 98/99, 1997 December 10 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - African 98/99, 1996 December 18 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - African 96/97, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - African Collection, 1995-1998 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - ALA, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - ALCTS, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - American Academy of Arts/Sciences, 1998 March 31 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - AMS, 1996 January (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Annual Reports, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Annual Reports 97/98, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Annual Reports 98/99, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - AOB 96/97, 1996 December 10 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - AOB 98/99, 1997 December 12 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Archiving, 1995-1999 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Area Curators, 1993 February 22 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Area Studies, 1997 June 8 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Art, 1998 January 20 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Art, 1999- 2000 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Art 96/97 Drama, 1996 February 9 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Art 97/98, 1996 December (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Art 98/99, 1997 December 8 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Arts of the Books, 1988-1998 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Arts of the Book 99/00, 1998 December 15 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Association of American Libraries, 1997 January 23 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - AUL, 1999 July 6 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - AYA, 1999 May 31 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Bibliographers, 1995 September (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Cal-Tech Conference, 1998 February 27 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Cambodia Genocide, 1999 September 10 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Cameron La Chair Collection, 1998 June (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Cancopy, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Cataloging, 1998-2000 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Cataloging: Remote Access, 1997 July 14 (Box 3, Folder 72)